a few months ago
um I did a
funeral and
uh I just kept thinking in my mind
this I'm not doing this for my brother
he's going to
live so
um to be here right now doing this is
our
surreal and
uh I know there are a lot of
wise and when Sean passed I started
asking the question
why and the Lord spoke to me and has
been speaking to me and so I want to
talk to you today about the
why uh Psalms 116 and verse1
15 the Bible says
precious in the sight of the Lord is the
death of his
Saints that's a very strange verse
precious in the sight of the Lord is the
death of his Saints why is it
precious why is
it
valuable why is it expensive why is it
costly why is it worth much to God the
death of his Saints what does he use it
for that's the question I want to answer
today
so when my brother and I were growing up
when we came from
Jamaica and came to the
states um one of the things that we did
every day was we played Batman and
Robin every
day every single day I was
Batman and he was
Robin and if you ever watched Batman and
Robin it was always like a cliffhanger
at the end of every episode
Batman and Robin were going to die for
sure this time but you had to stay tuned
for the next time and and Batman was
always saving Robin and that was me and
Sean every
day we were born 10 months
apart um but we were like
twins we came to the states we got on
the break dancing together we got into
the martial arts
together and by the way while we would
fight I would make sure that I never hit
my
brother especially in the
face so I'd let him do his thing then
I'd show him who the boss
was but I always cared for him that I
would never hurt my brother and I never
did we got the same best friend
we went to colleges close to each other
we had the same group of
friends
X-Men Sean Penny cook Mark small back in
uh
Freeport ahed
tamrad we had the whole we did
everything together we got into the
music together we were baptized together
as
Baptists and then years later we would
be baptized together on the same day as
seventh day
Adventists we were in the music industry
together we were dancers together then
rappers
together we decided to walk away from
Fame together I remember the day that I
went to sea I was like Sean I got to
tell you something I'm walking away from
the group and he was like I came to the
same conclusion
myself we walked away from the music
together we ended up going to the same
Adventist College together we both
married California
Girls we both became
Pastors in September of
2023 I had
this overwhelming sense of depression I
don't know where it came from I had no
idea what was going on with me I thought
I was I thought I was just losing my
mind the spirit of De
depression came over me it was
unexplainable and it would not
leave and I remember that as a result of
this I ended up writing something
because I just been thinking about death
and and what heaven's going to be like
in the reality of Heaven because the
world just got so dark to
me and I ended up
writing this story called Heaven's
diary and there was a a a a story of a
man who was coming up in the
resurrection of Christ and he's
chronicling he's he's journaling his
journey from the grave to the kingdom of
heaven at the second coming of
Jesus and I remember after writing it it
took me 7 days to write it and put it to
music and after writing it I started
sending it out to people my Ministry my
family and people who listened to it
were like blown away this is amazing how
did you write this and I would tell them
I don't know it just kind of came over
me because I just had this sense of just
like what is this world if there is no
Heaven one of the last discussions my
brother and I had before his voice
started going was about Heaven's diary
he listened to it and he and I were
talking about how Heaven is going to be
such a awesome place of the things that
we're going to do there things that
people don't even think about and that
as as his voice was
going the journal began with these words
awake awake he's hearing the voice of
the Son of God and he says the last
thing he remembered was him being
surrounded by his family as he was
slipping into death and now he's hearing
the voice of
God on March 8th Sean was diagnosed with
cancer March 7th he was diagnosed with
cancer and I remember thinking to
myself n
Sean we have a huge family huge sha is
the king of Health in our
family nobody took care of their health
more than my brother so not
Shawn a and if Shawn does have cancer
then if anyone's going to beat it is
it's going to be
him it's going to be him because Lord
that would be too crazy to have cancer
fall on the person who says I'm going to
take care of my body and live to the
glory of God that would that would
be and so when he was diagnosed with
this I want you to understand that that
Batman kicked in
when sea was in 11th
grade 12th grade and I was in my first
year of
college and Sean called me up Mom and
Dad were up in New York and Sea called
me and told me that some guys came to
the
house trying to fight him and it was the
only time Sean ever made a call to me
like
that so I got off the phone
got on the phone my best friend tamarat
I was like T we have
beef he said what's going on I said I
need you to get everybody I need you to
get everybody you
can to he's at Virginia Union I'm at
Virginia state and in a matter of an
hour there are five car
loads five carloads of us
driving down to Fredericksburg Virginia
my my parents aren't home my father
collects
guns we emptied the house of the
guns every
car praise
God that God we're here today that means
everything turned out all right so don't
even go further to well what happened
we're here today nobody's in
jail we're here
but that was a kind of protection that I
had for my
brother and so becoming a Christian now
that's kicked in for the glory of
God so now I'm like Sean okay we're
going to fight this we are going to pull
out every weapon against cancer that we
can we're going to fight this Sean
I got together a prayer
team we're GNA we're going to pray
everything that Sean's going through
every treatment that he has we're going
to be praying that that if his blood
count needs to be this we need to know
everything that's going on with Sean and
we're going to pray for a miracle
because my brother will be healed
and I didn't realize that I had been
watching a miracle until after my
brother
died
when they told sea that he had
cancer and that they had to do surgery
immediately and they had to put a tra
into his throat and they were going to
have to put a feeding bag into him
because he wouldn't be able to eat
anymore and his voice may not return and
they had stage four esophagal can
esophagal cancer
and they had to put him in a surgery
that
day I was in
Alabama and I remember when he was going
into the surgery and I thought to myself
how is this possible how was my
brother's life about to change so
dramatically in one day in one day he
goes from everything is fine it's just
strep throat to you have cancer you may
not be able to talk again you will not
be able to eat again in and all that
could come to my mind was
job and I remember in a
sense that that diagnosis to my brother
was like that it was like they were
diagnosing
me and when they did the
surgery then a FaceTime my brother after
and I was expect I don't know what I was
expecting to see but what I saw I was
not expecting to
see because beyond the tra beyond the
feeding
tool my
brother sees me on FaceTime and he does
this Sean how you doing
I don't know about you but to have a
voice for 50 years and then suddenly be
told you may never speak
again to love eating and and cooking and
to be told that you will not be able to
taste to be Erica Meyer's
son and be told that you will not be
able to experience her
cooking and I looked at my brother and I
thought to myself okay he's in shock
right
now but when he wears off I'm going to
be there for him
because th this is not this can't be
happening to my
brother and he's going to be overwhelmed
pretty soon and so I watched him that
day and I was just a amazed I was
just and I said he's in shock but it
it'll wear
off and we began going to
work everything that we could
do everything that we could
do
supplements
herbs looking into natural remedies
every day for 10
months our whole family we were
researching we were doing everything we
possibly
could and I have to tell you that it
feels like everything that could
possibly go
wrong everything that could possibly go
wrong just when we thought okay we're
we're we're hitting the turn here it's
about to get better oh he got an
infection and because of the infection
because the way they put the tube in
this happened and now that set him back
and I remember watching my brother
brother through this entire
trial and I began to think to myself
he's
Batman how is he batmanning right
now how is he doing this right now now
you know he and I we're listen when when
we became Christians yeah y when we
became
Adventists yall
know I think every everybody was afraid
to be around
us because y'all heard why every one of
y'all needed to be Adventist you
remember that family you remember that
none of you
escaped nobody when y'all saw us coming
y'all were like all right time to
go because if if we don't escape now
they going and this was me and Sean for
everybody
friends family uncle aunt it didn't
matter who you were
you knew we were coming for
you what
we what we found that led us to walk
away
from
Fame and
money from the bottom of our hearts we
wanted it wasn't just to okay I know
this now I'm
good we wanted everybody to know what we
had learned we wanted everybody to know
and experience the joy that we had
had and so Sean and I you know we we
grew in this and we walked in this and
and here's the thing you guys like y'all
know that out of you know with me and
Shawn my Ministry went public so people
knew me as the public speaker and Shawn
was just you know in his Corner doing
his
thing and and people were like oh pastor
s your sermon about the blueprint and
your sermon about this and and I saw
this on YouTube and that on YouTube and
I began to realize as I was watching my
brother that my brother was preaching a
sermon greater than anything I have ever
that has ever come out of my
mouth as I watched
Sean
live this
thing in the midst of a trial
I promise
you that I began to question my own
Christianity I mean maybe Sean did it
too because he and I talked and and Roar
and toning we would always talk about
man you know this person died and that
person died and man what must that be
like and and I I think in some
way God gives his Saints a supernatural
thing I don't know how to explain
it the Bible tells us to consider the
ant consider the
ant how it
gathers in the Harvest so that when
winter rolls around it's not found
wanting
and what I want you to understand
everyone is that my
brother my brother even though he walked
away from money he was
rich he was he had money in the
bank please understand what I mean when
I say he had money in the back I'm
talking about faith
money he had Faith dollars he was a
billionaire a and the reason why he was
such is because he learned the art of
investing he bought while it was
low my brother invested while the cost
of Faith was low and so it's funny
because we were looking at his phone the
other day and we Sean has videos on his
phone he didn't release them to anybody
it's just videos of him picking up his
phone and doing stuff like
this all right
God it's time again and then you see him
look at the phone and then you see him
open the gate to his backyard and he
walks into the gate and he's like let's
do this and the video
ends
Sean what were you doing with
God and what did it have to do with the
backyard like help
me nobody knew he was doing these videos
so on his phone he' be sitting in his
car and uh what was the
song the goodness of God it's PL and
he's just in the car and he's looking at
the phone and he's crying and he's
pointing
up and he looks at the phone and the
video
stops those intimate moments with God
he was he was becoming rich so that he
had money when an emergency he had
enough funds for that rainy
day when the crisis hit my brother had
enough in his wallet to handle
it he was rich in faith and I thought to
myself how many of us do not realize
that we are that we are
poor that we might talk about God and
and say we love God but but if you were
faced with a job like
situation would you have enough money in
the bank to handle the tribe the way you
have the way God wants you to handle it
and I watch you guys as my brother would
struggle to breathe mucus coming out of
his trie as he's struggling to breathing
I'm like Sean and in my mind I'm just
like I'm going to go crazy for my
brother I cannot watch this I cannot see
this Lord this is my little brother Lord
let's do
something and every time I asked my
brother Sean how you
doing Sean how you feeling
better with his whisper
better and I'm like Sean how how are
you doing
this
precious in the sight of the Lord is the
death of his Saints
not everybody dies
well not everybody who claims to be a
follower of the Lord walks into the
valley of the shadow of death fearing no
evil so when it happens
precious ah want you to look at this
now see in my mind it's the the job
story so you know we don't mind the job
story because in the job story job
lives and he gets a double portion at
the end of his oh hey give me a job
story if I can get the double portion
yeah so we want the job story but we
forget how often we forget that there's
a Jesus story
too that Jesus actually had to
die he actually went into the grave and
so in my mind I'm like all right Lord
this is a job story we're going to see
Shawn through up until Shawn's last
breath in my mind I'm like now the Lord
watch this the Lord's about to pull
something through watch
this and so when my brother took his
last breath yall need to
understand
how the question question why and I know
I'm a
pastor I know Pastor you're you're the
Christian I know I know the verses you
know the trumpet will sound I know all
of
that but I have to tell
you Lord Lord help me to understand
this help me to understand
this you know what people going to say
they're gon to say oh the H living
healthy what difference does that make
look at Sea serving God what difference
look at Shawn look at
Shawn they're going to say look at
Shawn that's why I shouldn't follow God
that's why it doesn't matter how I live
and the Lord said no they're going to
say look at
Sean look at
Sea look at how he lived his
life look at how he faced what every one
of us is going to
face look at how he smiled day by day
look at how when he was told your
terminal everybody in the room including
the doctor is crying and sea is there
like I didn't realize it
then but the miracle that we had been
praying for was happening before my
eyes I feel like my brother is that
character in the
bible let me say this way in my brother
I feel like I met an actual Bible
character like someone whose
story I began to understand that that
okay Lord you allow this to happen like
just as the devil came to Jo to God and
said I know job is your servant but I
bet you that if I do this this this this
and this that he will curse you to your
face and all I can say is that God
trusted my brother
enough to allow the guy that is the
healthiest person in the family who
doesn't drink who doesn't smoke who
lives his I'm going God trusted him
enough to use his life as a
demonstration
what if Jesus
lived 10 more
years father wouldn't his life wouldn't
he have been able to accomplish
more
no in Jesus's
death he would save more than he did
when he was alive
oh so
so the death of Jesus was precious
because through his death other people
came to the
Lord that's why it's
precious that's why it's costly that's
why God can say all right life completed
now look at that
life look at how he lived his
life so in the song
strange my my brother in the chorus
quotes Psalm 1 yall probably heard it
blessed is the man that walketh not in
the counsel of
the chanting
it blessed is the
man that walketh not in the
counsel of the ungodly nor standeth in
the way of Sinners nor sth in the seat
of the scornful but his Delight is in
the law of the Lord and in his law does
he meditate day and night and then this
verse he shall be like a tree planted by
the rivers of waters that bringeth forth
his fruit in his season his Leaf shall
also not wither and whatsoever he doth
shall prosper you know I've read this
verse a thousand times and it was not
until it was not until I Was preparing
this
message that I realized
something a
tree comes from a seed that has been
planted in the
earth I've always thought this verse was
talking about how a person lives their
life and and as they're living their
life their fruit will prosper but you
got to understand that a tree in order
for a tree to to grow something must
first go into the
ground and this is when it hit
me my brother's
life is like a
seed planted into the
ground that is going to bring forth
fruit to the glory of
God I did a tribute to my brother on
YouTube and then I connected Heaven's
diary with it because when he was dying
one of the last things he listened to
the day before he died I said Sean you
want to listen to Heaven's diary and he
was like
yeah and as he as we he put I put it on
and it was playing and the whole family
was around and the words awake
awake and then the person saying the
last thing I remembered was being
surrounded by my loved ones it is then
that it hit me it is then that I
remembered it is then that I thought to
myself Lord tell me that I wasn't
writing this from for my
brother how are we in a hospital room
right now with my brother dying and
we're surrounding him and he's listening
to this how is Lord were you was your
hand in this were you preparing us for
this months a year earlier before it
happened and as my brother is listening
to to to the to the part where he where
there ascend into heaven and he starts
doing this with his
hands if y'all have seen the video he
starts doing this and I'm there on the
bed with him and and we start doing this
together and I'm thinking to
myself
Sean I said
Lord give me a double portion of the
spirit that my brother has
give me a double portion of that spirit
let me tell
you thousands of people have listened to
that heaven's
diary and if that's thousands of seeds
that have been
planted to the glory of God because of
Shawn's
death if there are people in here right
now who as a result of this this moment
will walk away and say you know what I
wasn't considering God before I wasn't
considering Jesus before but now I might
consider
him if in the Kingdom of
Heaven There are those of you who are in
here today who will say
Sean do you
remember when you were telling me about
the Lord and I was
like the way you die
died the way you
died that was the
seed that started me on my journey to
God I'm G tell you something in that
Resurrection morning when Jesus comes
the Bible says Jesus is going to come
and all who are asleep in the grave will
be resurrected so that we enter Heaven
at the same time together like a family
reunion
if sea
hears that you are here because of his
death he's going to be like
no you
serious come on
Jesus that's what he's going to
do you know it that's what he's going to
do because my brother was that type of a
guy
he made you feel like you were the best
at whatever it is you were
doing he made you feel like you were the
I would come to fredburg and and go with
Shawn to the gym and Shawn would
introduce me to people in the gym like
this is his best friend ow meet so and
so and I'm just looking at this guy like
okay hi and sea is acting like he is his
best
friend and the pride he had in in in in
in in having me meet his friend and then
having his friend meet his older brother
this is my older brother
Al let me tell you there is nothing sea
would love more than to be like
Jesus Remember the cousin I'd pray I was
praying to you about remember the Auntie
the uncle the friend this this is him
this is her
precious in the sight of the
Lord is the
death of his
Saints Lord why wouldn't you let my
brother
live he has so much more to do he's got
a family Lord why wouldn't you let him
live
and the Lord says through his
death many more will be
saved I have a statement I want to read
in then I'll
close one of my friends sent this to
me it's just a paragraph here's what it
says
patience as well as courage has its
victories by meekness under
trial no less than by boldness and
Enterprise Souls may be one to
Christ the Christian who manifests
patience and cheerfulness under
bereavement and suffering who meets even
death itself with the peace and calmness
of an unwavering faith May accomplish
for the gospel more than he could have
affected by a long life of faithful
labor often when the servant of God is
withdrawn from active duty the
mysterious Providence which our
shortsighted vision would
lament is designed by God to accomplish
a work that otherwise would never have
been done
my brother showed us how to die
right he not only showed us how to
live he showed us how to die
right when we started keeping the
Sabbath we had understood that the
Sabbath was all about rest taking that
day to rest
and and God was teaching us how to rest
and how to rest under circumstances and
rest under trial and every seven day was
like a drill okay now I know you got all
these things going on but I want you to
take this time to
rest and seeing my brother
rest all the way through this
trial I would ask his kids
guys did you see your father cry cuz I
never saw him cry did
you y'all never just walk by the living
room and just caught
them you know it's
real when in your own
house with your own
children with your own spouse where
where you let your hair down so to
speak you know it's real
when
even among the
closest of your
companions they can say
truly this was a child of
God so I'm closing with an
[Music]
appeal because Sean would want me
to he's sleeping now
Resurrection morning is
coming but he's going to ask
me Al what did you do at my
funeral and I'm going to be like
Sean come
on the week before he
died no three 3 days before he died we
had been out here for 2 weeks we went
back to Alabama because we thought
everything was Sean was on the up and up
when we landed we got the call that we
had to come back because he only had a
few days and when I heard that I
FaceTime my brother I was in my
daughter's our daughter's apartment when
we got that word and I FaceTime Rowan
cuz he was there at the hospital and he
was in the room with sea Shawn was
sleeping when I FaceTime I was
crying I was stunned I was in shock I
was crying I I lost it and my brother
woke up and he saw me
crying and then he looked at me like
this in the midst of my Tears he looked
at me and he was like ow what are you
doing and I was like Sean Sean I'm sorry
I'm sorry all right I'm
good that's the kind of
[Music]
Faith every time I think of my brother
suffering
the cancer has gone to his liver the
cancer has gone to his lungs necrom
Matic pneumonia who gets that in their
last days your lungs are now being eaten
from the
inside you can't breathe you can't talk
you can't walk the cancer is in your
bones everything in his body is broken
except his spirit
the sermon my brother
preached is greater than anything that
has ever come out of my
mouth and I had to say Lord search
me search
me give me a double portion of that
spirit
[Music]
if there's anyone here
today I'm not going to ask you to stand
up I'm not going to ask you to raise
your hand but I'm making this
appeal Sean wants to see you in the
Kingdom of
Heaven he's going to ask me Al what did
did you and I'mma say yeah Sean I did
I told them I invited
them the way Sean's death would not be
in
vain is when people hear how he died and
see his life that they'll be like you
know what yeah I'm willing to walk away
I'm willing to walk away from my million
dollars whatever that is I'm willing to
walk away from my fame from my glory I'm
willing to do that because the example
Le that I've seen in this man has
changed my life so if there's anyone
here
today who will even entertain the
thought of coming to follow Jesus I pray
that you will do
[Music]
that I pray that a seed will be planted
today in your
heart that will find its fulfillment
and us being together at that great
family
reunion that is only possible because of
the blood of
Jesus let's not make his death be in
vain I appeal to
you what does it profit a man if he gain
this whole world and yet lose his soul I
appeal to
you I appeal to you friends
family everybody I appeal to
[Music]
you follow
Jesus give your heart to
him not in the oh yeah okay I
look at my brother's example and see
what it means to actually follow Jesus
my brother did not live a double
standard he was not one foot in the
world one foot in the church he followed
Jesus and those of you that know him
know that he was a man of his
word heavenly
father thank you Lord
[Music]
thank you for allowing me to still work
with my
brother thank you Lord that through his
death there will be people who have come
to know
you thank you that his death is precious
in your
sight so Lord ease our pain ease our
suffering
in when we cry Lord remind us that
sea when he was alive would look at us
and say what are you crying
for thank you
Jesus for calling Shawn to follow you
the way that he
did May his death glorify your
name in Jesus name we pray
amen
[Applause]